[{"answer": "No, that's your job", "docId": "Custody.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "No one's getting shot today, my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Do you know why you're here today, Mr. my friend", "docId": "Custody.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Are you being rhetorical", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Why am I here", "docId": "Custody.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Are you asking me", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Yes, but..", "docId": "Custody.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I do", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Really", "docId": "Custody.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Potty train? my friend", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Yes, baby", "docId": "Custody.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "We do have a normal life... for us", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Yeah, Insurance. That thing that covers medical emergencies", "docId": "Custody.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Everybody has insurance", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I can't do it Daddy", "docId": "Custody.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I can't do it", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "You can do it", "docId": "Custody.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Would you do it for a nickel", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I can't do it", "docId": "Custody.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I can't do it", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "This is my friend. This is my friend, and the little guy from the potty, is my friend. Guys, this is my friend and..", "docId": "Custody.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "My mom tells great stories", "docId": "Custody.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "That's okay, I don't have a dad", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I'm all about second chances, but not when I come in second place", "docId": "Custody.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Why was she here? What was that", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Someday", "docId": "Custody.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Someday is someday, baby", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Can you help him", "docId": "Custody.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "What does he need", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I don't know", "docId": "Custody.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Well, guys, I guess this is it", "docId": "Custody.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Yes we can", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " I won't", "docId": "Custody.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "No, you shouldn't have", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I could have looked sad", "docId": "Custody.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "But I look sadder. NICHOLAS I sad", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "This isn't about the kids", "docId": "Custody.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "It's about me, the selfish prick", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "If I give you my heart will you promise to treat it softly? Kiss it when it hurts? Put it in a box and know that it belongs to you", "docId": "Custody.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "I said I love you", "qsentId": 42}]